[
  {
    "question": "When was c language discovered?",
    "optionA": "1962",
    "optionB": "1972",
    "optionC": "1982",
    "optionD": "1992",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which was first programming language?",
    "optionA": "C",
    "optionB": "Fortran",
    "optionC": "C++",
    "optionD": "Haskel",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "When was first computer virus found?",
    "optionA": "1990",
    "optionB": "1980",
    "optionC": "1986",
    "optionD": "1984",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is first lady Programmer?",
    "optionA": "Angela Markel",
    "optionB": "Madam Curie",
    "optionC": "Elizabeth",
    "optionD": "Lady Augusta",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which was first computer game created?",
    "optionA": "space war",
    "optionB": "mario",
    "optionC": "dave",
    "optionD": "counter strike 1.6",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "When was rust language first appeared?",
    "optionA": "2009 March 7",
    "optionB": "2011 July 7",
    "optionC": "2010 July 7",
    "optionD": "2012 April 7",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Q in QBasics stand for?",
    "optionA": "quit",
    "optionB": "quick",
    "optionC": "quote",
    "optionD": "quite",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What function is automatically called in low level language program?",
    "optionA": "main",
    "optionB": "abs",
    "optionC": "next line",
    "optionD": "getline",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was original name for java?",
    "optionA": "ada",
    "optionB": "c++",
    "optionC": "oak",
    "optionD": "lisp",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What organization sets standards that are used across the internet?",
    "optionA": "Apple",
    "optionB": "Google",
    "optionC": "Microsoft",
    "optionD": "The world wide web consortum",
    "answer": "4"
  }
]
